// [{
//     "question" : "can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "its",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "its",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "how say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "its n awesome",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "its n awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "about the course how can you say  css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "awesome its",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "awesome its",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "a css fan boy, can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "are its awesome",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "are its awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "are category a html fan boy, can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "in awesome category",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "its awesome category",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "html",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "is really an html fan boy, can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "its category of",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "its category of",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "html",
// },
// {
//     "question" : "is really a html fan boy, can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "Is awsome",
//             "i have no words",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "its awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
    
// },
// {
//     "question" : "is gee really a javascript fan boy, can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//                 "i have no words",
//                 "not sure for that",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "not sure for that",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "javascript",
    
// },
// {
//     "question" : "how can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "am satisfied",
//             "i have no words about js",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "am satisfied",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "javascript",
    
// },
// {
    
//     "question" : "| js for aliens can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "i love js",
//             "i have no words about js",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "i love js",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "javascript",
    
// },
// {
    
//     "question" : "is_ css for aliens can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "it may be awesome",
//             "i have no words about css",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "it may be awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
    
// },
// {
    
//     "question" : "man, of css for aliens can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "pretty awesome",
//             "i have no words about css",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "pretty awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "css",
    
// },
// {
    
//     "question" : "man of js for aliens can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "no awesome",
//             "i have no words about css",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "no awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "javascript",
    
// },
// {
//     "question" : "tr of js for aliens can you say about the course css tell us your vision",
//     "options" : [
//             "is awesome",
//             "i have no words about css",
//             " its a trashy course",
//             " very bad"
//     ],
//     "answer" : "is awesome",
//     "level" : "beginner",
//     "category" : "javascript",
    
// }]